Guide to the Records of the American Institute of the City of New York for the Encouragement of Science and Invention 1808-1983 (bulk, 1828-1940) MS 17
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Children's Fair Years, 1921-1983
  - Subseries 1: Student Events and Programs, 1928-1983
    Science Congress - The Science Congress was an annual series of scientific meetings for members of the Junior Science Clubs. The congress was modeled on the scientific meetings of the American Association for the Advancement of Science and the adult meetings of the American Institute. Beginning in 1933, junior and senior high school students lectured, read scientific papers, and gave demonstrations of their work at the congress. In 1934, Christmas lectures modeled on the Christmas series at the Royal Institution of London became part of the congress which was held at the end of each year. Some of the Christmas Lectures were broadcast on the radio by NBC. There is no material on the Science Congress from 1940-1966. Material for a 1967 Junior Academy Science Congress is included in this subseries. It is unclear if the Science Congresses continued after that time. The Science Congress material includes applications to the congress, the topics of the talks and demonstrations of the students, ticket information, and attendance records.
    Accent on Science - This was a short-lived American Institute weekly radio program that ran on WNYC in 1937. It was a fifteen-minute segment that consisted of conversations with members of the science community on various topics including chemical warfare, telescopes, the cures and causes of syphilis and gonorrhea, and the proper food to serve on airlines. The material includes transcripts of most of the shows and correspondence regarding plans for the program.
    Scholastic Salon of Photography The Scholastic Salon of Photography was originally part of the Children's Science Fair, but it became a separate event in 1938 due to its popularity. Sponsored by the American Institute and several camera clubs from New York City schools, students from across the country submitted photographs to the salon and prizes were awarded to the winners. Prize winning photographs and selected entries were placed on display at the American Museum of Natural History. After the second salon, the winning photographs traveled to schools around the country for display. The Salon material includes brochures, correspondence, planning material, and publicity information for 1938-1940. Only a few photographs from the salons are in the collection.
    Science Laboratory - After the success of the student laboratory at the 1939-1940 World's Fair, the American Institute started a permanent laboratory where students could experiment on their own outside of school. The lab was located in Manhattan on Fifth Avenue. By late December of 1941, the lab was closed due to a lack of funds. The material includes administrative information, correspondence, photographs, and examples of experiments performed in the laboratory.
    Crime Prevention Bureau Courses - In 1933, the American Institute sponsored courses to officers of the Crime Prevention Bureau of the New York Police Department on establishing science clubs. The NYPD hoped that establishing science clubs, similar to their establishment of athletic activities, would help prevent juvenile delinquency. There is administrative material on the planning of these courses and events, with evaluations on of their progress.
    - Children's Science Fair, 1928 (Offsite-box 512, Box 140)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1928-1929 (Offsite-box 512, Box 141)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1929 (Offsite-box 513, Box 142)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1930 (Offsite-box 513, Box 143)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1931 (Offsite-box 514, Box 144)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1931-1932 (Offsite-box 514, Box 145)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1932 (Offsite-box 492, Box 146)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1932 (Offsite-box 492, Box 147)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1932 (Offsite-box 493, Box 148)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1932 (Offsite-box 493, Box 149)
    - Children's Science Fair, Junior Science Club, 1932 (Offsite-box 494, Box 150)
    - Junior Science Club, 1932 (Offsite-box 494, Box 151)
    - Junior Science Club, 1932 (Offsite-box 495, Box 152)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1933 (Offsite-box 495, Box 153)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1933 (Offsite-box 496, Box 154)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1933 (Offsite-box 496, Box 155)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1933 (Offsite-box 497, Box 156)
    - Children's Science Fair, Junior Science Club, 1933 (Offsite-box 497, Box 157)
    - Junior Science Club, 1933 (Offsite-box 498, Box 158)
    - Junior Science Club, 1933 (Offsite-box 498, Box 159)
    - Junior Science Club- Bronx, 1933 (Offsite-box 499, Box 160)
    - Junior Science Club- Brooklyn-Queens, 1933 (Offsite-box 499, Box 161)
    - Junior Science Club- Queens-Staten Island, Science Club Course for Police Officers, 1933 (Offsite-box 502, Box 162)
    - Junior Science Club, Science Club Course for Police Officers, Club Membership, 1933-1934 (Offsite-box 500, Box 163)
    - Junior Science Club- Membership, 1934 (Offsite-box 500, Box 164)
    - Junior Science Club- Membership, Science Congress, 1934 (Offsite-box 501, Box 165)
    - Junior Science Club- Science Congress, Museum Courses, 1934 (Offsite-box 501, Box 166)
    - Junior Science Club- Museum Courses, Christmas Lectures, 1934 (Offsite-box 502, Box 167)
    - Junior Science Club- Christmas Lectures, Junior Activites, 1934 (Offsite-box 503, Box 168)
    - Junior Science Club- Junior Activites, 1934 (Offsite-box 503, Box 169)
    - Junior Science Club- Workshop Courses, Zone Meetings, 1934 (Offsite-box 504, Box 170)
    - Junior Science Club- Zone Meetings, Other, 1934 (Offsite-box 504, Box 171)
    - Childrens' Science Fair, 1935 (Offsite-box 505, Box 172)
    - Childrens' Science Fair, 1935 (Offsite-box 505, Box 173)
    - Childrens' Science Fair, 1935 (Offsite-box 506, Box 174)
    - Childrens' Science Fair, 1935 (Offsite-box 506, Box 175)
    - Student Science Clubs, 1935 (Offsite-box 507, Box 176)
    - Student Science Clubs- Membership, 1935 (Offsite-box 507, Box 177)
    - Student Science Clubs- Membership, Junior Activities, Central Meeting, 1935 (Offsite-box 508, Box 178)
    - Student Science Clubs- Planetarium Visit, Christmas Lectures, 1935 (Offsite-box 508, Box 179)
    - Student Science Clubs- Science Congress, Bibliography, 1935 (Offsite-box 509, Box 180)
    - Student Science Clubs- Bibliography, Workshop Courses, 1935 (Offsite-box 509, Box 181)
    - Student Science Clubs- Workshop Courses, 1935 (Offsite-box 510, Box 182)
    - Childrens' Science Fair, 1936 (Offsite-box 510, Box 183)
    - Childrens' Science Fair, 1936 (Offsite-box 511, Box 184)
    - Childrens' Science Fair, 1936 (Offsite-box 511, Box 185)
    - Childrens' Science Fair, Junior Science Clubs- Membership, 1936 (Offsite-box 515, Box 186)
    - Student Science Club- Membership, Central Meeting, 1936 (Offsite-box 515, Box 187)
    - Student Science Club- Science Congress, Christmas Lectures, 1936 (Offsite-box 516, Box 188)
    - Student Science Club- Workshop Courses, 1936 (Offsite-box 516, Box 189)
    - Student Science Club- Workshop Courses, 1936 (Offsite-box 517, Box 190)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1937 (Offsite-box 517, Box 191)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1937 (Offsite-box 518, Box 192)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1937 (Offsite-box 518, Box 193)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1937 (Offsite-box 519, Box 194)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1937 (Offsite-box 519, Box 195)
    - Student Science Club- Membership, 1937 (Offsite-box 520, Box 196)
    - Student Science Club- Science Congress, 1937 (Offsite-box 520, Box 197)
    - Student Science Club- Workshop Courses, 1937 (Offsite-box 521, Box 198)
    - Student Science Club- Workshop Courses, "Accent on Science" Radio Programs, 1937 (Offsite-box 521, Box 199)
    - "Accent on Science" Radio Programs, 1937 (Offsite-box 522, Box 200)
    - "Accent on Science" Radio Programs, Children's Science Fair, 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 522, Box 201)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1938 (Offsite-box 523, Box 202)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1938 (Offsite-box 523, Box 203)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1938 (Offsite-box 524, Box 204)
    - Student Science Clubs, 1938 (Offsite-box 524, Box 205)
    - Student Science Clubs- Science Congress, Salon of Photography, 1938 (Offsite-box 525, Box 206)
    - Student Science Clubs- Salon of Photography, Workshop Courses, 1938 (Offsite-box 525, Box 207)
    - "Accent on Science" Radio Programs, 1938 (Offsite-box 526, Box 208)
    - "Accent on Science" Radio Programs, Children's Science Fair, 1938-1939 (Offsite-box 526, Box 209)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1939 (Offsite-box 527, Box 210)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1939 (Offsite-box 527, Box 211)
    - Children's Science Fair, 1939 (Offsite-box 528, Box 212)
    - Children's Science Fair Floor Plans, Student Science Clubs, 1939 (Offsite-box 528, Box 213)
    - Student Science Clubs, 1939 (Offsite-box 529, Box 214)
    - Student Science Clubs, Photography Salon, 1939 (Offsite-box 529, Box 215)
    - Student Science Clubs- Workshop Courses, Science Congress, 1939 (Offsite-box 530, Box 216)
    - Student Science Clubs- Science Congress, 1939 (Offsite-box 530, Box 217)
    - Student Science Clubs- Workshop Courses, Photography Salon, 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 531, Box 218)
    - Student Science Clubs- Photography Salon, 1940 (Offsite-box 531, Box 219)
    - Student Science Clubs- Photography Salon, 1940 (Offsite-box 532, Box 220)
    - Student Science Clubs- Workshop Courses, 1940 (Offsite-box 532, Box 221)
    - Student Science Clubs- Workshop Courses, Student Laboratory (Offsite-box 533, Box 222)
    - Applications for Student Laboratory, 1940-1941 (Offsite-box 533, Box 223)
    - Student Science Clubs- Science Congress, Student Laboratory, 1941 (Offsite-box 534, Box 224)
    - Student Fairs, Science Congress, 1942-1967 (Offsite-box 534, Box 225)
    - Student Fairs, Science Congress, 1967-1893 (Offsite-box 535, Box 226)
    - Junior Science Clubs from NYC Boroughs- Index Cards, 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 430)
    - Children's Science Fair- Card List, 1932 (Offsite-box 431)
    - Children's Science Fair- Card List, 1933 (Offsite-box 432)
    - Children's Science Fair- Card List, 1935 (Offsite-box 433)
    - Children's Science Fair- Card List, 1935 (Offsite-box 434)
    - Science and Engineering Fair- File Cards, 1939 (Offsite-box 435)
    - Science and Engineering Fair- File Cards, 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 436)
    - Photographic Salon- Index of Entries, 1939 (Offsite-box 437)
    - Third Scholastic Salon of Photography- Entry Blanks, 1940 (Offsite-box 438)
    - "Red Magic Page" from The World (oversize), 1927-1928 (Offsite-box 456)
  - Subseries 2: Adult Programs, 1921-1941
    This subseries contains material relating to the American Institute's adult programs from 1921 to 1941, which included lectures, exhibitions, luncheons, demonstration lectures, science roundtables, medal award (for scientific achievement) and other dinners, forums, 'get-togethers,' field trips, picnics, and movie nights (scientific topics).
    The amount and type of material for each program or event varies. Common items include correspondence, speeches or lectures, invites and invite lists, announcements, work requisitions, cash statements, mailing lists, calendars, press releases, ticket records, regrets, and menus.
    General subjects of various adult programs and events ranged from science and technology to health and medicine. Biology, astronomy, and psychology were also broad areas of study. From 1921 to 1929, lectures discussed agriculture, electricity, aeronautics, anatomy and health, energy, astronomy, and radiation. Some annual fair material, and items pertaining to the Centenary Dinner (1928) can also be found here.
    Lecture and roundtable topics from 1930 to 1932 included criminology, aviation, monorails, heredity, animal virus diseases, rocketry, birth control, eugenics, relativity, t.v. and radio, cancer, cosmic rays, x-rays, vitamins, biology, and sterility. Programs from 1933 to 1934 discussed vitamins, geology, cells, science education, mental disorders, aviation, geometry, physics, farming, chemical engineering, crime, oxygen, population, radioactivity, and weather forecasting.
    1935 demonstration meetings presented experiments with liquid air and chemicals, electricity, and steel alloys. Roundtables discussed botany, deep sea fish life, the social philosophy of race survival, chemical engineering, animal behavior, the Hayden Planetarium, insect control, and telescopes. Field trips were made to New York City subway car shops, and the American Museum of Natural History for a behind the scenes tour.
    Topics for 1936 events included the scientific method, research, biology, television, telescopes, prefabricated houses, gases, cellulose, genes, blood tests and parentage, x-rays, insanity, and earthquakes. Programs and events during 1937 included discussions of mental hygiene, allergies, radioactivity, vitamins, radio, hormones, color photography, ESP, aviation, and organic chemistry. 1938 meetings dealt with air conditioning, isotopes, radio, meteors, patents, and photography.
    From 1939 to 1941, a program entitled Short Courses in Science covered such topics as flying, neuroses, patents and inventions, atoms, genetics, psychiatry, bridge building, hormones, and insects. Demonstration meeting topics included lie detectors tests and roundtables discussed caffeine. Field trips were made to the Dept. of Agriculture and Western Union.
    - Exhibitions, Dinners, 1921-1929 (Offsite-box 535, Box 227)
    - Luncheons, Medal Award Dinners, 1930-1932 (Offsite-box 536, Box 228)
    - Round Tables, 1932 (Offsite-box 536, Box 229)
    - Round Tables, Medal Award Dinners, 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 537, Box 230)
    - Round Tables, 1933 (Offsite-box 537, Box 231)
    - Round Tables, 1933-1934 (Offsite-box 538, Box 232)
    - General Meeting, Medal Award Dinner, 1934 (Offsite-box 538, Box 233)
    - Medal Award Dinner, 1934 (Offsite-box 539, Box 234)
    - Medal Award Dinner, 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 539, Box 235)
    - Medal Award Dinner, 1935 (Offsite-box 540, Box 236)
    - Lectures, 1935 (Offsite-box 540, Box 237)
    - Round Tables, 1935 (Offsite-box 541, Box 238)
    - Round Tables, Medal Award Dinners, 1935-1936 (Offsite-box 541, Box 239)
    - Anniversary and President's Dinner, 1936 (Offsite-box 542, Box 240)
    - Meetings, Lectures, 1936 (Offsite-box 542, Box 241)
    - Meetings, Round Tables, 1936 (Offsite-box 543, Box 242)
    - Round Tables, Medal Awards Dinner, 1936-1937 (Offsite-box 543, Box 243)
    - Dinners, General Meetings, 1937 (Offsite-box 544, Box 244)
    - Meetings, Lectures, 1937 (Offsite-box 544, Box 245)
    - Meetings, Lectures, 1937 (Offsite-box 545, Box 246)
    - Medal Award Dinner, General Meeting, 1938 (Offsite-box 545, Box 247)
    - Meetings, 1938 (Offsite-box 546, Box 248)
    - Meetings, Round Tables, 1938 (Offsite-box 546, Box 249)
    - Meetings, Forums, 1938 (Offsite-box 547, Box 250)
    - Medal Awards, 1938-1939 (Offsite-box 547, Box 251)
    - Medal Awards, Courses in Science, 1939 (Offsite-box 548, Box 252)
    - Round Table, Members' Night, 1939 (Offsite-box 548, Box 253)
    - Medal Awards Dinner, Science Courses, 1940 (Offsite-box 549, Box 254)
    - Science Courses, Medal Awards Dinner, 1940-1941 (Offsite-box 549, Box 255)
    - Members' Night, Science Courses, 1941 (Offsite-box 550, Box 256)
  - Subseries 3: Administrative, 1921-1983
    Most of the material in the this Administrative subseries consists of bills, receipts, accounts, correspondence, reports, and membership lists. The material from the period after 1980 consists almost entirely of cancelled checks, deposit lists, and bills.
    Correspondence - Most of the correspondence is to and from officers and employees of the American Institute, and concerns the everyday business of the Institute, such as finances, membership, letters of thanks to speakers, etc. Some of the topics addressed throughout the period 1921 - 1940 are: the future and purpose of the American Institute, the status of the Institute's investments and its solvency, relations with the state and municipal governments, rentals of venues for events, and publications of the American Institute. Specific topics include the merger of the American Institute with the New York Electrical Society in 1930; a conflict during the same period over control of the Institute; the Chicago World's Fair of 1932; a dispute by the Institute with the American Institute for the Scientific Care of the Hair over the name of the latter organization; and the affiliation school science clubs with the Institute.
    Persons represented in the correspondence include trustees and officers of the Institute, such as Dr. Morris Meister, H.T. Newcomb, L.W. Hutchins, and Dr. H.H. Sheldon. Also represented throughout the 1930s is Frances Flanagan, the Institute's secretary.
    Reports - Includes Treasurers' Reports, and reports of various committees, such as the Membership Committee, and Committee on Elections.
    Business and Financial Records - Includes bills, vouchers, and cancelled checks, usually for everyday expenses of the American Institute. Some material, primarily from the 1930s, deals with the investments of the Institute, and for some years, primarily in the 1930s, the material includes ledger sheets documenting the Institute's finances. Also included are time sheets of various employees of the Institute.
    Minutes - Most of the minutes are of Trustees meetings. Other minutes include those of specific committees of the American Institute, such as the Finance Committee.
    Membership information - This material includes applications and proposals for membership, lists of lapsed, deceased, or delinquent members, and material relating to membership drives.
    - Correspondence,Vouchers and Checks, 1921-1922 (Offsite-box 550, Box 257)
    - Checks and Vouchers, Old Information Files, 1923 (Offsite-box 551, Box 258)
    - Reports, Checks, and Vouchers, 1924 (Offsite-box 551, Box 259)
    - Reports, Checks, and Vouchers, 1924-1925 (Offsite-box 552, Box 260)
    - Correspondence, 1925 (Offsite-box 552, Box 261)
    - Correspondence, Speeches, Old Information Files, 1925 (Offsite-box 553, Box 262)
    - Speeches, Vouchers, 1925-1926 (Offsite-box 553, Box 263)
    - Board of Membership Meetings, Correspondence, 1926 (Offsite-box 554, Box 264)
    - Bank Information, Correspondence, Old Information Files, 1926 (Offsite-box 554, Box 265)
    - Old Information Files, Correspondence, 1926-1927 (Offsite-box 555, Box 266)
    - Vouchers and Checks, Correspondence, 1927 (Offsite-box 555, Box 267)
    - Correspondence, Reports, 1927 (Offsite-box 556, Box 268)
    - Old Information Files, 1927 (Offsite-box 556, Box 269)
    - Old Information Files, 1927 (Offsite-box 557, Box 270)
    - Old Information Files, 1927 (Offsite-box 557, Box 271)
    - Old Information Files, Annual Report, 1927 (Offsite-box 558, Box 272)
    - Vouchers for Cash Paid, 1928 (Offsite-box 558, Box 273)
    - Vouchers for Cash Paid, Resigned Members' Files (A-D), 1928 (Offsite-box 559, Box 274)
    - Resigned Members' Files (E-P), 1928 (Offsite-box 559, Box 275)
    - Resigned Members' Files (S-Z), Deceased Members' Files, 1928 (Offsite-box 560, Box 276)
    - Correspondence, 1928 (Offsite-box 560, Box 277)
    - Correspondence, 1928 (Offsite-box 561, Box 278)
    - Annual Reports, Activities Committee, 1928 (Offsite-box 561, Box 279)
    - Old Information Files, 1928 (Offsite-box 562, Box 280)
    - Expense Vouchers, 1929 (Offsite-box 562, Box 281)
    - Financial Information, 1929 (Offsite-box 563, Box 282)
    - Correspondence, Annual Reports, Meetings, 1929 (Offsite-box 563, Box 283)
    - Membership, Old Information Files, Vouchers, 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 564, Box 284)
    - Vouchers, Membership Committee, Ballots, 1930 (Offsite-box 564, Box 285)
    - Ballots, Correspondence, 1930 (Offsite-box 565, Box 286)
    - Correspondence, Annual Report, 1930 (Offsite-box 565, Box 287)
    - Correspondence, 1930 (Offsite-box 566, Box 288)
    - New York Electrical Society, Vouchers and Checks, 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 566, Box 289)
    - Checks and Vouchers, Financial Statements, 1931 (Offsite-box 567, Box 290)
    - Membership, Correspondence, 1931 (Offsite-box 567, Box 291)
    - Correspondence, 1931 (Offsite-box 568, Box 292)
    - Correspondence, Dinners, Annual Reports, 1931 (Offsite-box 568, Box 293)
    - Duplicate Checks, 1932 (Offsite-box 569, Box 294)
    - Financial Statements, 1932 (Offsite-box 569, Box 295)
    - Investment Records, Time Sheets, 1932 (Offsite-box 570, Box 296)
    - Time Sheets, 1932 (Offsite-box 570, Box 297)
    - Time Sheets, Deceased and Resigned Members, 1932 (Offsite-box 571, Box 298)
    - Deceased and Resigned Members, Correspondence, 1932 (Offsite-box 571, Box 299)
    - Correspondence, Finance, Investments, 1932 (Offsite-box 572, Box 300)
    - Correspondence, Meetings, Associations, 1932 (Offsite-box 572, Box 301)
    - March of Science Files, Annual Reports, 1932 (Offsite-box 573, Box 302)
    - Checks and Vouchers, 1933 (Offsite-box 573, Box 303)
    - Checks, Records of Requisitions, 1933 (Offsite-box 574, Box 304)
    - Investment Records, Time Sheets, 1933 (Offsite-box 574, Box 305)
    - Resigned Members' Files, 1933 (Offsite-box 575, Box 306)
    - Resigned Members' Files, 1933 (Offsite-box 575, Box 307)
    - Membership Programs and Committees, 1933 (Offsite-box 576, Box 308)
    - Correspondence, 1933 (Offsite-box 576, Box 309)
    - Correspondence, 1933 (Offsite-box 577, Box 310)
    - Annual Reports, Memorandums, 1933 (Offsite-box 577, Box 311)
    - Board Meetings, Quarterly Meetings, 1933 (Offsite-box 578, Box 312)
    - Subject Information, March of Science Files, Annual Report, 1933 (Offsite-box 578, Box 313)
    - Checks and Vouchers, 1934 (Offsite-box 579, Box 314)
    - Record of Requisitions, 1934 (Offsite-box 579, Box 315)
    - Finances, Time Sheets, Record of Requisitions, 1934 (Offsite-box 580, Box 316)
    - Associate Memberships, Other Files, 1934 (Offsite-box 580, Box 317)
    - Associate Memberships, Correspondence, 1934 (Offsite-box 581, Box 318)
    - Program Committees, Quarterly Meetings, 1934 (Offsite-box 581, Box 319)
    - Demonstration Meetings, Committes, Other Meetings, 1934 (Offsite-box 582, Box 320)
    - March of Science Files, Annual Reports, Checks and Vouchers, 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 582, Box 321)
    - Checks and Vouchers, 1935 (Offsite-box 583, Box 322)
    - Work Requisitions, 1935 (Offsite-box 583, Box 323)
    - Financial Reports, Time Sheets, Membership, 1935 (Offsite-box 584, Box 324)
    - Membership, 1935 (Offsite-box 584, Box 325)
    - Resigned and Associate Membership (A-P), 1935 (Offsite-box 585, Box 326)
    - Resigned and Associate Membership (Q-Z), 1935 (Offsite-box 585, Box 327)
    - Membership Campaign, Correspondence, 1935 (Offsite-box 586, Box 328)
    - Annual Reports, Dinners, Committees, 1935 (Offsite-box 586, Box 329)
    - Committees and Events, 1935 (Offsite-box 587, Box 330)
    - Committees and Fellowships, 1935 (Offsite-box 587, Box 331)
    - Checks and Vouchers, 1936 (Offsite-box 588, Box 332)
    - Checks and Vouchers, Requisitions, 1936 (Offsite-box 588, Box 333)
    - Requisitions, Financial Statements, 1936 (Offsite-box 589, Box 334)
    - Membership Committees, 1936 (Offsite-box 589, Box 335)
    - Medal Awards and Committees, 1936 (Offsite-box 590, Box 336)
    - Membership, Awards, Dinners, 1936 (Offsite-box 590, Box 337)
    - March of Science Files, Annual Reports, Checks and Vouchers, 1936-1937 (Offsite-box 591, Box 338)